https://efcst.org/terms-conditions/

COPYRIGHT
The information available on this website is the property of the Epilepsy Foundation Central & South Texas and is protected by copyright and other intellectual property laws. Information contained herein may be displayed, reformatted, printed or downloaded one time for your personal, noncommercial use only. You agree not to reproduce, retransmit, distribute, disseminate, sell, publish, broadcast or circulate the information on this website, unless you have received specific permission from the Epilepsy Foundation Central & South Texas. Any copy made of information obtained from this website must include the copyright notice.
DISCLAIMER OF WARRANTIES AND LIABILITY
The information contained on this Web Site is for information purposes only, and you assume full responsibility and risk for the appropriate use of medical information contained herein. Do not make changes in your medication or lifestyle as a result of any information you receive on this Site, without consulting your physician. The Epilepsy Foundation Central & South Texas does not intend to provide medical or legal advice, and does not directly or indirectly practice medicine or dispense medical services. Consult your own physician or lawyer for specific advice about your personal situation.
The Clinical Care section of this web site is intended to provide information to physicians and health care professionals about the current treatment and understanding of the epilepsies. Laypeople who read this information are warned against making any changes in their treatment based upon the information here without consulting their personal physician. While the Foundation has made every effort to ensure the accuracy of this information, medical knowledge changes quickly, and changes may have occurred since this information was last reviewed by professionals. Information may also not be complete; the practitioner is therefore urged to continually seek up-to-date information, and may contact the Epilepsy Foundation Central & South Texas for assistance in doing so. Some treatments recommended in this section of the website, while in line with generally accepted best medical practice, may not be approved by the U.S. Food and Drug Administration for the described uses. Consult the Physicians’ Desk Reference and product manufacturer for approved uses and additional information.
While the Epilepsy Foundation Central & South Texas takes pride in providing accurate and up to date information about epilepsy and its consequences, there may be omissions or inaccuracies in such information and on this Web Site. The Epilepsy Foundation, its officers, directors, employees or agents, does not warrant or guarantee the accuracy or completeness of its information or services, and specifically disclaims any liability therefore.
LINKS
Periodically throughout this site, you will notice links to other sources of epilepsy-related information and services. The Epilepsy Foundation Central & South Texas does not recommend, endorse or guarantee the adequacy or reliability of those other sources of information and services.
NOTICE OF COPYRIGHT INFRINGEMENT
The following agent has been designated to receive notification of claimed infringement of copyright regarding information contained on this website:
Sindi Rosales
Epilepsy Foundation Central & South Texas
10615 Perrin Beitel Rd #602
San Antonio, TX 78217
(210) 653-5353
PRIVACY STATEMENT
The Epilepsy Foundation Central & South Texas wants to protect the privacy of visitors to our website. We also would like to use the information that our visitors share with us for our own purposes, in order to improve the quality of our services, and to promote public understanding and education about the impact of epilepsy on people’s lives. The Foundation has adopted the following privacy policy governing its website. The privacy policy is continuously being revised to refine it and we welcome your thoughts which you may send via messages to Staff@EFCST.org.
What personally identifiable information does the foundation collect from me?
The Epilepsy Foundation Central & South Texas respects the personal privacy of the visitors to our website. We believe keeping your information private and in a secure environment is very important. When you browse our website, you do so anonymously. Personal information is not collected, unless you voluntarily provide us with that information as described below. We will not share with third parties your name, street address, telephone number or e-mail address without your consent. We do not sell or rent your personal information. We will not deliver target advertisements from others to you. We provide no mechanism for an advertiser to reach you, unless you sign up directly with an advertiser or outside vendor.
In order for the EFCST.org website to improve its performance and design and to provide you with better services, we track the usage of our website through information taken from our server log files. The type of information collected is basic statistical data, such as channels and sections viewed, time of access and amount of time, search phrases used to reach the Foundation’s site, and browser type. This information is anonymous, and is collected in the aggregate; it will not personally identify you in any way, and we cannot get back to you the user through this data. We use this aggregated information in order to learn what are the most popular sections of our site, for general promotional purposes and for making decisions about the future strategy and direction of the website. The aggregated information may also be shared with third parties to promote Epilepsy Foundation Central & South Texas services and the website, or to add to general knowledge concerning the public’s need for epilepsy education and treatment services.
What happens when I sign up with the Foundation online?
You voluntarily provide us with personal information when you choose to become a member, make a donation, join our Speak Up Speak Out grassroots network or Newsroom, join one of our e-Communities, subscribe to one of our e-newsletters, participate in a research campaign and when you purchase a product from our catalog. The information we collect through these transactions includes such things as your name, address, phone number, email address and, when you make a financial transaction, your credit card number. This allows the Foundation to send you messages and to share information with you that we think you may find useful. We study our users’ demographics, interests and behavior based on this information voluntarily provided for a variety of reasons, including to have better information on the needs of people with epilepsy and how to improve our services.
What is a cookie and how does the Foundation use them?
When you voluntarily join one of the Foundation’s e-communities, make a donation, or purchase an item from the Foundation, a cookie is placed on your computer hard drive. A cookie is a small amount of data stored as a text file. The data contains a unique identification number assigned by our system that recognizes your browser when you come to our computer, but does not recognize you as an individual. These cookies remain on your system and are automatically retrieved when you return to our website at a later time. We use cookies to remind us of who you are in order to send you information you have requested and deliver to you a more personalized service. The cookie also allows us to automatically log you in to certain sections of our site without having you re-enter user name information for each return visit.
You may choose to set the Internet properties of your computer so that you are alerted each time a cookie is being stored on your computer or you may choose to prohibit the collection of cookies all together. In addition, you may delete cookies that have already been stored on your hard drive. If you do prohibit the collection of cookies, understand that you will need to re-enter your email and other information each time you go to the portion of our website which requires the input of identifying information.
How do I change my personal information or stop receiving online information from the Foundation?
If you decide that you no longer want to be a part of an e-community, or receive marketing or other information from the Foundation sent to your online email address, you may unsubscribe by following the prompts made available within the email in question. If you are a member of the Foundation and would like to update your records, please contact us at Staff@EFCST.org.
How does the Foundation protect my confidential information?
If you have shared with us your credit card number in order to purchase an item from our marketplace or to make a donation to the Foundation, your credit card number is stored on a secure server and is protected by firewalls. The Foundation uses computer encrypted technology to protect your information and this information is kept confidential. The Foundation sometimes contracts with outside vendors and business partners to fulfill customer services and hosting services on the website. When we do so, we enter into confidentiality and non-disclosure agreements with all vendors stating that they will hold information received through our site confidential and will not sell or share user information to any third party or use the information for their own personal use. A very limited number of the staff of the Epilepsy Foundation Central & South Texas has secure access to data. We hold our employees accountable for our privacy principles and each employee is personally responsible for maintaining customer confidence in the company.
The Foundation may disclose information to law enforcement and other authorities in the rare case when there is reason to believe that disclosure is necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against someone who may be causing injury to or interference with (either intentionally or unintentionally) the Epilepsy Foundation Central & South Texas’ rights or property, other Foundation’s users or anyone else that could be harmed by such activities. We may disclose or access account information when we believe in good faith that the law requires it.
Children Under 13
Do not send us any information about yourself or your family if you are under age 13 — including information like your name, address or email address — unless you have asked your parents for permission to do so. The Foundation will not knowingly request personal identifying information from children under the age of 13 without parental consent. If we learn that we have personal information from a child under 13, we will delete that information from our database as soon as possible.
Linked Internet Sites
The Foundation hyperlinks to numerous sites that we believe are of interest to people with epilepsy. We do not control the privacy policies of business partners, advertisers, sponsors or other sites to which we may provide hyperlinks, and the privacy policies of any of these third parties may differ from ours. When you hyperlink to the website of one of our business partners, advertisers, sponsors, or other sites, you are subject to their privacy policies and not those of the Foundation. The Epilepsy Foundation Central & South Texas is not responsible for such provisions and expressly disclaims any and all liability related to the privacy policy or practices of such other websites.
Where should I go if I have a question or a complaint about the Foundation’s privacy policy and practices?
If you have any additional questions about your privacy on the Foundation’s website, or if you believe that your privacy may have been violated by the Foundation, please feel free to contact us at Staff@EFCST.org.
OUR GUIDING PRINCIPLES
“Our Guiding Principles” was developed by the national staff of the Epilepsy Foundation Central & South Texas to guide the personal actions and professional performance required to reach our strategic goals and achieve our vision.
Ethics in Dealings
We support each other and interact in an honest and forthright manner in all that we do;
We do not participate with others in any transactions that are not in the best interest of the Epilepsy Foundation Central & South Texas and the people we serve;
We observe all laws and regulations that apply to the Epilepsy Foundation Central & South Texas and to work that we do.
Relationships with Stakeholders
We give personal, prompt, and thorough attention to the needs of each individual who has epilepsy and to each family we serve;
We make certain that people who have seizures, their families, and loved ones know of our dedication and passion for eliminating the stigma of seizure disorders;
We make every effort to provide personal, prompt and thorough attention to the needs and requests of our colleagues;
We recognize our affiliates and sponsors as key stakeholders and conduct our partnerships with them accordingly;
We ensure that respect, dignity, compassion, kindness, and grace are the hallmarks of all of our interactions with others.
Quality of Work
We each contribute toward creating a work environment that celebrates collaboration and shared goals;
We take pride in ensuring that the result of our personal actions contributes to the good reputation of the Epilepsy Foundation Central & South Texas;
We each take responsibility for, and are satisfied with nothing less than, delivering excellence in the quality of what we do.
Diversity in Our Working Environment
We maintain a reputation for integrity and diversity in our recruitment, hiring, staff development and retention policies and practices;
We encourage, promote and celebrate diversity in all its aspects;
We seek diversity of belief, thought, and experience in making important decisions within the organization;
We respect individual opinion and amicably agree to disagree when our views cannot be reconciled;
We share information fully and accurately with all staff in order to facilitate collaborative, effective, and efficient teamwork;
We promote a friendly and inviting working atmosphere that encourages all staff to interact, share ideas, and participate in activities;
We provide all staff personnel with professional growth and learning opportunities wherever and whenever possible;
We recognize and promote staff members, equitably and on merit;
We acknowledge and reward staff achievements in a manner that encourages productivity, consistent performance, and personal fulfillment.
Leadership in the Healthcare Field
We build and preserve a reputation for integrity, independence, accuracy and objectivity in representing the needs of people with epilepsy;
We work to establish the Epilepsy Foundation Central & South Texas as a leader in its field through best-of-class management and quality response to the needs of our stakeholders;
We strive to develop a significant and strong public following in support of the work of the Epilepsy Foundation Central & South Texas on behalf of its stakeholders;
We are tireless in promoting the development and implementation of public and private sector policies meeting the needs of people with epilepsy, their families and our other stakeholders.
San Antonio 8601 Village Dr #220
San Antonio, TX 78217
Phone: (210) 653-5353
Fax: (210) 653-5355
Email: Staff@EFCST.org
Austin 12741 Research Blvd #401
Austin, TX 78759
Phone: (512) 876-8471
Epilepsy Foundation Central & South Texas is a 501(c)(3). © 2020
